<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Curs Android Fundamentals</string>
    <string name="hello_world_from_android">Hello World from Android!</string>
    <string name="this_is_my_first_textview">This is my first TextView</string>
    <string name="i_am_a_button">I am a button</string>
    <string name="write_your_name_here">Write your name here</string>
    <string name="i_accept_terms_and_conditions">I accept Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="change_color">change color</string>
    <string name="search_for_android">Search for androids</string>
    <string name="please_add_your_name_here">Please add your name here</string>
    <string name="greetings">Greetings :)</string>
    <string name="error_insert_name">Please insert a name</string>
    <string name="textview_3">TextView 3</string>
    <string name="textview_2">TextView 2</string>
    <string name="textview_1">TextView 1</string>
    <string name="long_text">Of course, you’d want to replace the URL after git remote add upstream with the appropriate clone URL for the original project repository. For the rest of this article, I’m going to assume you used upstream as the name for this additional Git remote. Now, you could try pushing changes to the original repository using git push at this point, but it would probably fail because you probably don’t have permission to push changes directly to the repository. Besides, it really wouldn’t be a good idea. That’s because other people might be working on the project as well, and how in the world would we keep track of everyone’s changes? That’s where branches come in.</string>
    <string name="text_on_the_right">text on the right</string>
    <string name="text_centered_in_parent">text centered in parent</string>
    <string name="start_mainactivity">Start MainActivity</string>
    <string name="start_recyclerview_activity">Start RecyclerView Activity</string>
    <string name="start_constraint_activity">Start Constraint Activity</string>
    <string name="this_is_a_textview_in_a_constraintlayout">This is a TextView in a ConstraintLayout</string>
    <string name="this_is_a_long_text_view_content">this is a long text view content</string>
    <string name="button">Start Second Activity</string>
    <string name="start_firstactivity">Start FirstActivity</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="browser">Browser</string>
    <string name="use_device_with_sim">Please use a device with an active SIM</string>
    <string name="hello_from_first_activity">hello from first activity</string>
    <string name="sample_startactivityforresult">Sample startActivityForResult</string>
    <string name="confirm_message">Yes, I\'m here! :)</string>
    <string name="text_one">Text One</string>
    <string name="text_two">Text Two</string>
    <string name="text_three">Text Three</string>
    <string name="first_text">All animals are composed of cells, surrounded by a characteristic extracellular matrix composed of collagen and elastic glycoproteins. During development, the animal extracellular matrix forms a relatively flexible framework upon which cells can move about and be reorganised, making the formation of complex structures possible. This may be calcified, forming structures such as shells, bones, and spicules. In contrast, the cells of other multicellular organisms (primarily algae, plants, and fungi) are held in place by cell walls, and so develop by progressive growth. Animal cells uniquely possess the cell junctions called tight junctions, gap junctions, and desmosomes.\n
With few exceptions—in particular, the sponges and placozoans—animal bodies are differentiated into tissues. These include muscles, which enable locomotion, and nerve tissues, which transmit signals and coordinate the body. Typically, there is also an internal digestive chamber with either one opening (in Ctenophora, Cnidaria, and flatworms) or two openings (in most bilaterians).</string>
    <string name="second_text">Animals are monophyletic, meaning they are derived from a common ancestor. Animals are sister to the Choanoflagellata, with which they form the Choanozoa. The most basal animals, the Porifera, Ctenophora, Cnidaria, and Placozoa, have body plans that lack bilateral symmetry. Their relationships are still disputed; the sister group to all other animals could be the Porifera or the Ctenophora, both of which lack hox genes, important in body plan development.\n
These genes are found in the Placozoa and the higher animals, the Bilateria. 6,331 groups of genes common to all living animals have been identified; these may have arisen from a single common ancestor that lived 650 million years ago in the Precambrian. 25 of these are novel core gene groups, found only in animals; of those, 8 are for essential components of the Wnt and TGF-beta signalling pathways which may have enabled animals to become multicellular by providing a pattern for the body\'s system of axes (in three dimensions), and another 7 are for transcription factors including homeodomain proteins involved in the control of development.[99][100]</string>
    <string name="third_text">Animals (also called Metazoa) are multicellular, eukaryotic organisms in the biological kingdom Animalia. With few exceptions, animals consume organic material, breathe oxygen, are able to move, can reproduce sexually, and go through an ontogenetic stage in which their body consists of a hollow sphere of cells, the blastula, during embryonic development. Over 1.5 million living animal species have been described—of which around 1 million are insects—but it has been estimated there are over 7 million animal species in total. Animals range in length from 8.5 micrometres (0.00033 in) to 33.6 metres (110 ft). They have complex interactions with each other and their environments, forming intricate food webs. The scientific study of animals is known as zoology.\n
Most living animal species are in Bilateria, a clade whose members have a bilaterally symmetric body plan. The Bilateria include the protostomes—in which many groups of invertebrates are found, such as nematodes, arthropods, and molluscs—and the deuterostomes, containing both the echinoderms as well as the chordates, the latter containing the vertebrates. Life forms interpreted as early animals were present in the Ediacaran biota of the late Precambrian. Many modern animal phyla became clearly established in the fossil record as marine species during the Cambrian explosion, which began around 542 million years ago. 6,331 groups of genes common to all living animals have been identified; these may have arisen from a single common ancestor that lived 650 million years ago.</string>
</resources>